nissanforums.com 2002-12-07

# GFoS Inc. User Agreement

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to GFoS Inc. Because we care about your personal privacy, we describe here our information gathering and dissemination practices. Remember, this policy applies only to our site. When you leave our site through linking to one of our advertisers or vendors, you should always check their privacy policies as they may differ from our own 

**What Information Do We Collect?**

**IP addresses and cookies**  
We use your IP address to be sure that we know when a unique visitor is on our site, to diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. We may track the URL of the last website you visited before you came to GFoS Inc., and the URL you went to after leaving our site. We also use cookies to customize your experience on our site so it is compatible with your operating system and to deliver information to you customized to your specific interests. For example, if you visit featured stories about cars and equipment used for camping, we might advise you of products, services or new information geared to camping or other outdoor experiences. Your cookie is stored only on your own machine. It does not contain any credit card, address or other personal information, and is shared only with those vendors with whom you place an order. Some features are available on our site only through use of a cookie. You may usually disable our cookies on your browser, but if you do so, you may not be able to use certain features of our site, and we will be unable to optimally customize your visits to our site. 

Aggregate information on the number of visitors to the site, demographic information (like make and model of car owned, age, gender, and the like), and anonymous user profiles developed using these techniques, may be shared with our advertisers, affiliates and vendors. 

**Personal Information**  
You can visit our site, read articles and other materials, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. If you wish to purchase any parts or accessories online, however, you must establish a credit card account with us or our vendors. That necessitates collection of additional personal information, such as your full name, billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. 

We may offer you the opportunity to complete surveys online, to enter contests or sweepstakes or participate in polls. While most polls are anonymous, most surveys are not. You must provide personal information, however, to enter contests or sweepstakes in order for us to contact you if you win. Any personal information you provide, such as e-mail address, full name, street address, telephone number, hobbies or interests, type of car you drive, or any other information will be available to GFoS Inc., and may be available to our advertisers, vendors and promotional partners. We may use your personal information to notify you of other publications, products or services from us, our affiliates, vendors or promotional partners which might be of interest to you. If at any time you do not wish to receive such communications from GFoS Inc., you may opt out by e-mailing customerservice@GFoS.com.

If you purchase anything from our participating vendors, we and the vendor involved will maintain information about your transactions. We will also provide to all of advertisers, vendors and affiliates anonymous aggregate information about online transactions at this site. 

**How Do We Use Your Information?**  
Personally identifiable information will be used to fill your orders, to contact you in response to your questions; to provide you with notices about new products or services available from GFoS Inc., our vendors, advertisers and affiliates; and to advise you of administrative or other issues related to the site (such as any significant down time associated with scheduled or unscheduled maintenance). Although our vendors are solely responsible for fulfillment of orders, and for the safety and quality of the products and services they offer, your feedback may result in a decision to drop a vendor from our list. 

We use personally identifiable information about you and anonymous, aggregate demographic or user profile data to facilitate your use of the site, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to customize promotional messages and product offerings, as well as to develop and improve content, layout and services on the site in response to visitor interests. 

**What Information Is Disclosed To Others?**  
Both anonymous, aggregate data, and personally identifiable data will be shared with others as outlined below: 

Participating Vendors. To facilitate ordering through our site, GFoS Inc., will cache your order information, create an authorization with a merchant account (i.e., your credit card company) and give participating manufacturers, retailers, wholesalers or distributors the order information and authorization for the merchant bank. Any time you order from a participating vendor, they will automatically have all information related to the order. Participating vendors may use that information to advise you directly of other products and offerings that they provide. GFoS Inc., is not responsible for their privacy policies, and urges you to inquire about their information practices. In addition, all vendors will receive the same anonymous, aggregate data that our advertisers do. 

Advertisers and Promotional Partners. Anonymous, aggregate demographic information obtained from cookies and similar technology will be shared with our advertisers. Information such as type of car owned, gender, age, Income, hobbies and the like will be aggregated and shared with advertisers, vendors and affiliates in a manner which does not personally identify you. Credit card numbers, bank account numbers, and passwords are not shared with advertisers or promotional partners, and are only shared with specific vendors with whom you place an online order. 

Credit Card Companies. As in any transaction, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the vendor, item(s) purchased, and date and total cost. GFoS Inc., will not otherwise provide any data to your credit card company. 

Web Support Firms. There are many companies who may be required to assist GFoS Inc., in making this web site available to you. Web host firms, technical consultants, advertising agencies, and fulfillment firms for contests and promotions may have access to information on the site. All companies working for GFoS Inc., must comply with our information collection, use and disclosure policies, and are not permitted to sell your information to third parties or to use it except as authorized by us. Vendors and advertisers will also use technical and other consultants. You should inquire about their policies, as GFoS Inc., is not responsible for their privacy policies and procedures. 

GFoS Inc., parents and affiliates may access both anonymous, aggregate demographic data and any personal information you provide for internal marketing purposes, Including sending you notices of new publications, services or products likely to be of interest. They will not sell or share it with other third parties. 

Legal Authorities. GFoS Inc., reserves the right to disclose any personal information you provide where required by law, Including cooperating with law enforcement or other government officials, or in response to legal process by third parties. Your use of this site constitutes your express agreement to such disclosure as GFoS Inc., in its sole discretion, deems necessary or appropriate to meet any legal obligation or to cooperate in any legal investigation. 

We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt important information, such as your credit card data, in an effort to prevent unauthorized access. We Incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our service providers to maintain the security of your personal information to avoid its disclosure except as described in this policy. Although we use our best efforts to assure that your data remains secure when maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions cannot be assured. 

**Links**  
GFoS Inc. may offer links to other sites so that you can conveniently visit our vendors and advertisers. We are not responsible for their privacy policies and urge you to inquire about them before providing any personally-identifiable information. 

**What About Kids?**  
We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children   
under the age of 13. 

**Your Agreement**  
YOUR USE OF THIS WEB SITE CONSTITUTES YOUR EXPRESS CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY AND INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE INTO OUR USER AGREEMENT. THIS POLICY IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE. ANY MATERIAL CHANGES IN THE MANNER IN WHICH WE HANDLE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, HOWEVER, WILL BE POSTED HERE FOR 30 DAYS BEFORE THEY GO INTO EFFECT. CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE REVISED TERMS. 

**Contact Information**  
This site is operated by:
